Hey everyone, welcome to a new video. It's a boot video today because I received
new boots from Up2Step and they're special boots
So you will see what I mean in a sec because
so they're all the new boots but they do have this kind of belt thing that attaches them together
and they're really high and long and i'm honestly i i honestly don't know how to call them belted
boots, some kind of chaps. I'm not sure. If you have any suggestions, write it in the
comments and I'm going to put them on now and see how they're going to look. I saw these
kind of boots a few times and I always wanted to try them because I think they could be
a really interesting look. On the other hand, I have no idea how to style them yet, so I'm
going to start with the boots look now. Okay, I spontaneously decided to put them on over
I'm gonna put on this catsuit first to see how that looks and I have to find a way to get into them.
Ah, that's so long.
Oh, super.
Not like this again.
Oh
Okay, let me check.
I think they look really spacey due to the metallic silver color here and it's definitely
like a totally new look.
I haven't had anything in my closet like this until now and I'm very happy that they fit
in the legs and that they're not too wide.
I think that would have looked stupid.
Yeah, nice.
So yeah, I'm instantly reminded of chaps from like horse riding but I think belted boots
sounds cooler so I'm going to stick with that.
I mean the design feature is the belt and I think you can like replace the belt with a different one as well.
Let me get it up because I can simply like pull it out here.
And I would say without that it does look kind of stupid.
So these boots are definitely meant to wear with the belt and with this kind of hip holster thingy.
And without you would just opt for normal over-the-knee boots that end like here without that flappy thing.
I like the look with the catsuit because it's a one-piece thing underneath.
I think if you would opt for like jeans or pants and a separate top, it would start to look
overcrowded so to say or too much.
With all the different
yeah, the hemlines and the belt going on.
But I do have a second look prepared, the initial look I wanted to show you with the bodysuit.
First I have a little look here.
And now I'm going to switch outfits.
I don't feel this combination, I'm not happy with it, so I'm going to switch to the next one.
I still have another one.
I think this looks really cool.
I opted for kind of cowgirl look so to say I don't know with just a panty and a top
and the boots on top and I think the belt really emphasizes the back side of the outfit also the
cutout of the chaps here I really love this look and I think it works pretty well together
better than with the swimsuit before anyway and I also love the contrast here with the black and
silver so I think this is a really cool look where would I wear this to well since the outfit is
actually an exotic pole dance outfit this is definitely a really good outfit to dance around
the pole and yeah it has this look with the overknees and the shiny outfit that would look
really cool on the pole. Alright rating these boots or yeah giving a summary I think they're
really cool you have to put some thoughts into the outfits you can't wear with every outfit so
you have to find things that fit to them other than that I think it's a really cool look it's
something special and you sure have an eye catcher with them so I'm glad I own a pair of these now
I'll see when I'm going to use them for another video so keep your eyes open and
check out all my other videos thanks to up to step for sending these ones I
really like them and thank you for watching this video see you in the next
one bye